Shh! Don't wake up Fry.
Shh!
My roommate's sleeping!
Wake up already!
Huh?
I'm about to get down and funky with this ladybot,
and I'd appreciate
it if as many people
as possible
could know about it.
Now can we get
some privacy?
Oh, yeah!
Back it on up.
Hambone, hambone!
Hambone
Okay, hambone break's over.
Back to the bedroom!
Hambone, hambone!
Hambone
Wake up
and feel the coffee!
No, I'm late
for work again!
Sorry I'm late.
Well, well, well. Look who decided to show up.
I've had it with
your tardiness, Fry.
I expect you to arrive the
same time as everyone else.
Well, wait a second.
Leela's not here yet.
She left a while ago.
She said some idiot was taking
her to lunch for her birthday.
Oh, no, I'm late!
Since you got stood up, I thought
this might cheer you up a notch.
That's not necessary.
What day is today?
It's Leela's birthday
Please stop.
What a day for a birthday
I really would like
you to stop singing.
...cake!
You want to buy a slice of
birthday cake for $11.95?
Yes, please.
Ooh, nice cake.
Sorry, I'm late.
Where have you...
It's fine.
You're not mad?
I was.
But then I realized
it's actually my fault
for thinking you might be on time for once.
Anyhow,
I ate both our lunches.
You ordered
the lobster pileup.
It wasn't cheap.
Bam!
Please, let me
make it up to you.
I'll treat you to
a fancy birthday dinner
tonight, at Cavern
on the Green.
Wow, that'll be the nicest
place I've ever been stood up.
Not this time.
No matter what happens,
I swear I'll be there.
Guys, guys! Hedonismbot is
finally gonna settle down,
and marry a nice
house in the suburbs!
But tonight, he's having the
girls-gone-wildest bachelor party of all time!
Who cares?
I'm having dinner with Leela.
Just go to your
stupid party.
We can have dinner on my birthday some other year.
No! I can throw up
on a stripper anytime.
Tonight, I want to
not throw up on you.
Really?
Your loss.
Hey, Professor,
you're my wingman!
Very well. Cubert,
fetch my drinking teeth.
I just have to sign Leela's
birthday card. How do you spell X-O?
It's a record-your-own-message
card.
You don't sign it, you
leave a nude video greeting.
Does it have to be nude?
I guess not.
That never occurred to me.
If I leave now, record a
birthday greeting on the way,
score some fancy cologne
at the newsstand,
I'll be exactly on time.
You're not going anywhere!
But I have a date.
You were late this morning,
so you have to stay
and test my latest invention!
Behold!
A time-traveling machine!
Time?
I can't go back there!
But this time machine
only goes forward in time.
That way you can't
accidentally change history,
or do something disgusting, like
sleep with your own grandmother.
I wouldn't want
to do that again.
We're going to test it by going
forward in time one minute.
Get in.
Okay, hurry.
Let's get it over with.
I can record Leela's birthday
card while we're in there.
Happy birthday, Leela!
I'm really sorry
I'm gonna be one minute late,
'cause we're testing the
professor's dumb time machine, but...
Okay, I'll just
nudge us forward
exactly one minute
into the... Whoa!
My card!
Did we go too far?
What time is it?
The year 10,000.
Whoopsie.
Oh, dear.
I mean, oh, my.
The year 10,000?
But I promised Leela
I'd be on time for dinner!
Relax, Fry.
Everyone we ever knew died
thousands of years ago.
Everyone we ever knew?
I never liked those guys.
No! They did it!
They blew it up!
And then the apes blew up
their society, too!
How could this happen?
And then the birds took over
and ruined their society!
And the cows, and then, I don't
know, is that a slug, maybe?
No!
While you await
your "friend,"
allow me to read from a
prepared history of our cavern.
"These unique rock formations
"were created over millions
of years by mineral-rich water,
"dripping from
pores in the ceiling.
"Dripping and dripping,
year upon year,
"century upon century..."
What day is today?
Hey, aren't you the loser who got
stood up at my other restaurant?
Just shut up and
bring me two dinners.
Has anyone seen Fry's ass? It's
late for a date with my boot.
Fry's not here.
Obviously, he went to that pervert
party with Bender and the professor.
Fry went to the party?
We interrupt
Hypnotoad On Ice
to bring you breaking coverage of the
disaster at Hedonismbot's bachelor party.
Linda, what began as innocent
fun ended in tragedy tonight
when a nuclear-powered
robot stripper
suffered a catastrophic
reactor meltdown.
There is only one survivor.
Everywhere I looked,
there were piles of bodies.
And then
the explosion struck.
The three co-workers
I liked, all dead!
Fry stood me up and died?
I'm so angry!
I mean, I'm so sad!
But I'm still pretty angry!
But also sad.
Can I be both?
It's what he'd want.
Then that's what I am!
Man, the future is
a total craphole,
and whoever lives here is
a crap-faced sack of crap!
No offense, fellas.
Don't sweat it, man.
I'll never
see Leela again.
No, without a backwards time
machine, we're stuck in this craphole.
Dude, give it a rest.
Hold on. I've got it!
We can't go back in time,
but we can keep going forward
until people invent
the backwards time machine.
And then we can go home.
Hit it.
In the year 105,105
If man is still alive
If robot can survive
They may find
In the year 252,525
The backwards time machine
still won't have arrived
In all the world
there's only one technology
A rusty sword for
practicing proctology
In a future year
that ends with a 20
A shlubby merman's
gonna try to get chummy
He may look
like a watery wimp
When in fact he's
a bloodthirsty shrimp
In the year one
million and a half
Humankind is
enslaved by giraffe
Man must pay for
all his misdeeds
When the treetops
are stripped of their leaves
Sometimes I can't
believe how successful
Planet Express became
once the professor was killed
and you seized control.
There were tough times,
but we all pulled together.
I've been crunching
the numbers
on our
trans-galactic strategy...
What are you doing here?
I laid you off 20 years ago.
The claws can't flee
like they used to.
Success is nice, but I do
kind of miss the old days.
Hey, Leels.
Hi, Cubert.
May we help you,
strange ones?
We are travelers from the past, my good runt.
I see. Since your time,
human evolution has diverged.
There are we, advanced
in intellect and morality.
And the Dumblocks, stupid, vicious
brutes who live underground.
Advanced in intellect,
you say?
Have you invented
a backwards time machine?
No, but if we apply
our superior minds,
we could perfect such a device within five years.
See you then!
We're back for
our time machine!
Ow!
Yoo-hoo! Boys!
What's this era in
human history like?
The machines. We built them
to make our lives easier,
but they rebelled.
They won't stop until every human is dead.
This seems like a nice
future. Let's just stay here.
We could settle down
on that mountain of skulls.
Hey! That place had a
gorgeous view of Blood Lake!
Greetings, time travelers.
Stupid jerks! Wouldn't let
me stay in the good future.
How did you know
we're time travelers?
We, too, study
the time-travel enigma.
We have perfected a method using
negative-mass neutrino fields
that allows us to
travel backwards in time.
My name's Hubert.
All right!
We can go home!
We can talk of our
research tomorrow.
Men are very rare
in our society.
Even very old and
stupid males are prized.
Tonight, please be the guests of
honor at our fertility banquet.
Well, there's certainly no
harm in a fertility banquet.
I could eat.
And fertilize.
Very well. Let us anoint our guests
in oil without using our hands.
So, we can stay in the future you
like, but not the future I like?
Next!
No! I was about
to close the deal!
Bender, they had
a backwards time machine!
The other place had
a lot of good things, too!
Did you even see
that mountain of skulls?
Why, you!
Oh, no, you didn't.
Stop! Somewhere, sometime,
Leela is waiting for me.
We need to keep looking
for a backwards time machine.
Fry's right.
Yes. We have to work
together, not have this fight,
which I was
definitely winning.
The year one billion.
I've got a feeling
this could be exactly
the point in time
we've been looking for!
Nope.
In fact,
all life is extinct.
So let's keep going forward.
It's no use.
Earth is dead.
This is the end
of all things.
The Cavern on the Green.
I made it, Leela.
Sorry I'm
a billion years late.
You'll get your alimony
check, Cubert. Now get lost!
Chill out.
I'm just here to see Amy.
Move it, boy toy. Granny's
taking you to Atlantic City.
I don't know why you ever
married that pig-nosed punk.
I don't know, either.
I'm married to the job now.
I used to think there was
someone for me, but... Ow!
How odd. It's one of those old
record-your-own-message birthday cards.
Happy birthday, Leela!
I'm really sorry
I'm gonna be one minute late,
'cause we're testing the
professor's dumb time machine...
But, you know,
happy birthday and all, and,
I love you.
My card!
My whole life I've been mad at
him, and it wasn't his fault.
You know, all in all,
I had a good life.
What do you say the three of us grab a six-pack
and watch
the universe end?
Hear! Hear!
That's basically
what I do every day.
To the end of the universe!
So long, Earth. Thanks for the air and whatnot.
Whoa!
Hey, what was the
purpose of life anyway?
Who knows? Probably some
hogwash about the human spirit.
Sounds about right.
The stars
are receding.
Oh, the vast emptiness!
Yeah, yeah,
I can take a hint.
The last proton should be decaying about now.
Bye, last proton.
And, here we are.
The end of the universe.
Well, now what?
You guys want to talk?
No, thanks.
Did anyone else see that?
Unbelievable!
It's a second big bang!
My God, is it possible?
It must be possible.
It's happening.
By the way,
what's happening?
It appears this universe is
exactly identical to the old one.
If so, we just need to keep going forward in time
to the point when we left!
The Earth is born!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the moon!
Look. The first fish
to crawl up on land.
It was coming right at us!
You saw it.
I'm gonna grab
another beer.
Fry, Fry, you're missing the dinosaurs!
It's okay.
They're not going anywhere.
Where'd they go?
Now, what's going on there?
History.
Hang on. I just want to make one stop.
Easy, easy.
Taking her in
for a landing.
One year to go.
Six months.
I'm almost there, Leela.
One month,
two weeks, one hour,
30 seconds, and here we...
Whoa!
Stop!
Give me the keys, Magoo!
We'll have to
bring her around again.
Just slow it down. I'll
shoot Hitler out the window.
Darn! I hit Eleanor
Roosevelt by mistake.
Okay,
nearing our era again.
Here we go.
Careful this time.
Careful.
We're going to test it by going
forward in time one minute.
Get in.
Okay. Hurry.
Let's get it over with.
Uh-oh.
This new universe is about 10
feet lower than our old one.
Pow! We took care of
the time travel paradox.
All right!
Hooray!
Uh-oh. I'm late for
dinner with Leela.
Welcome to
Cavern on the Green.
May I offer you some meat loaf while you wait?
Sorry I'm late!
Actually, you're on time.
Really?
I have to admit, I was
afraid you wouldn't make it.
That was the old Fry.
He's dead now.
Happy birthday, Leela.
I got you a card, but I guess I kind of lost it.
That's okay.
I don't really like cards.
What I'll remember is
our time together.